5988 Respite Ct Johns Creek, GA 30097

Xuyang Zhang

(352)-222-6077 Zhangxuyang.chn@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Subject Matter Expert on Enterprise Mobility and Security with good track record of maintaining high CSAT score. Passionate about identifying product opportunities appealing to new customers, working with corresponding teams to materialize the features, and driving more product adoption with existing customers. Strong business sense with a master's degree focused on Information Systems and Operations Management from University of Florida.

EXPERIENCE

Senior Consultant

VMware (Atlanta, GA)

Nov 2020-Present

- Articulate solution design, integrating both technical and business concepts, and present a transformational journey to project stakeholders.
- Drive awareness and understanding of product strategy, roadmaps and best practices, amongst peers and customers
- Build Automation flows, and Power App used by 400+ people to boost team collaboration and efficiency

EUC Consultant VMware (Atlanta, GA) May 2018 – Oct 2020

- Designed and deployed VMware Workspace ONE suite in SaaS and On-Prem models for Enterprise Mobility Management and Identity & Access Management use cases across various sectors.
- Identified feature gaps and work closely with R&D team through design, implementation, and release
- Developed training materials and delivered training sessions on implementations and operations

Subject Matter Expert

VMware AirWatch (Atlanta, GA)

May 2016-May 2018

- Served as technical escalation point for internal employees and trusted advisor for customers
- Provided technical consultation and support to high-profile, strategic, and high-visibility customers
- Collaborated with R&D team to de-escalate P0 issues, and resolve production incidents in timely manner
- Participated in SRE team to continuously monitor and improve performance of hosted environments
- Created KBs and solution documentations which deflect over 500 support requests per month

•

Technical Support Engineer

AirWatch by VMware (Atlanta, GA)

Jan 2015-Apr 2016

- Reviewed and corrected 3rd party integrations including Directory, CA, VPN, Proxy, Syslog, Idp, etc.
- Troubleshot production issues through different angles including Server, Network, Database, Software, etc., achieving 98% CSAT score

EDUCATION

Gainesville, FL

University of Florida

Aug 2012-May 2014

- MSc in Information Systems and Operations Management with Minor in Auditing GPA: 3.8
- Courses: System Analysis and Design, Advanced Programming, Databases, Network, Finance, Accounting

SKILLS & AWARDS

- Enterprise Mobility and Security, Identity and Access Management, Architecture Design, SQL,
 Networking, Automation, PowerApps, Customer Service, Project Management, SDLC
- Deloitte Merit Scholarship (2013): Awarded for maintaining a 4.0 GPA